http://www.hampshireflag.co.uk/privacy.htm

Hand Waving Flags
Novelty Flags (5ft x 3ft)
Banner Systems
Banner Arms (Post Mount)
Banner Arms (Wall Mount)
Exhibition
Event Graphics (External)
Banner Frames
Exhibition Graphics (Internal)
Office Address
Unit 11Pipers Wood Industrial Park,Waterberry Drive,Waterlooville,HampshirePO7 7XUUnited Kingdom
Opening Hours
Our telephone lines are open 8 hours per day
Monday-Friday:
Home
Who are we?
Hampshire Flag Company LTD are a manufacturer and producer of hand sewn flags and promotional products specialising in providing high quality, bespoke designed products for a variety of clients.
In order to provide an effective service to our clients it is necessary for us to process personal data, including sensitive personal data therefore acting as a data controller under the GDPR.The main part of our business activities include producing designed products for our clients.
Your personal details
Your personal details may be given to us in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to the following:
•When you contact us for our services.
•When you use, or contact us through our website
•When you use our services.
•When you use or buy our products
•When you enter competitions.
•When you complete registration or order forms.
We must have a legal basis for processing your personal data. For the purposes of being able to provide the best service to our clients and to provide well designed and manufactured products, we will at times need to process your personal data.
We will only use your personal data in accordance with the terms of the following statement.
What are your rights?
•The right to be informed about the personal data that we process on you.
•The right of access to the personal data that we process on you.
•The right to rectification of your personal data.
•The right to erasure of your personal data in certain circumstances.
•The right to restrict processing of your personal data.
•The right to data portability in certain circumstances.
•The right to object to the processing of your personal data that was based on a public or legitimate interest.
•The right not to be subjected to automated decision making and profiling, and
•The right to withdraw consent at any time.
Where you have consented to us processing your personal data and sensitive personal data you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time by contacting the following e-mail address which is fully monitored by a trained individual:
privacy@hampshireflag.co.uk
Legal bases for processing your data
We believe that we have a legitimate interest in processing your data for the purposes of conducting business activities and other activities.
By processing your personal data, we believe that we are able to offer a more bespoke and professional service and that this is in all party’s best interests.
Our organisation provide a design and manufacturing service to clients and type of data we may hold includes, but is not limited to the following:
•Details of your key contact methods, including addresses, email addresses, phone numbers.
•Emails which may include personal data which have been sent to and from our organisation.
•Details of payments you have made, or are due to make
•Methods of payments that you have used, although we will never retain credit or debit card information.
We retain this information as we believe that it falls within our legitimate interest in providing our services to our clients.
Giving your consent
Sometimes it will be necessary for us to obtain your consent to process and hold your data, in particular when processing sensitive data.
In cases such as this you have the following rights:
•You have to give your consent freely
•You have to know what you are consenting to
•You should be able to control your consent
•We will keep a record of your consent
•You have the right to withdraw your consent
Collection of personal data
When working with our clients we will collect data that will help us ensure a fair and effective relationship.
Data we collect for this purpose will usually be basic.
This data could include, but is not restricted to:
•Names
•Addresses
•Date of Birth
•E-Mail Addresses
•Phone numbers
•IP addresses if you visit our website and agree to our cookies policy
•Car Registration numbers used for signing in purposes, should you visit us at our offices.
•Details of payment methods and payments that you have made, or due to make.
We collect personal data from you in the following ways:
Personal data that you give us:
•You contact us by phone or email
•We contact you by phone or email
•Information that you give us in person.
•When you communicate with us via our website
•Personal data we receive from other sources
•When you complete order or registration forms.
•When you enter competitions ran by the organisation.
Personal data that we receive automatically:
•IP Addresses
•Information and data we collect via marketing tools and by using our website and opening emails.
Using your Personal Data
Our primary function is to provide flag and bunting design, and production service to our clients. We will process your data in the following ways:
•Storing your data on our database, records system and/or server so we can contact you about your orders.
•Storing your data on our database, records system and/or server so we can contact you about our products and services.
•For targeted marketing campaigns.
•To help establish, exercise or defend a legal claim
Sensitive Personal Data
From time to time we may need to collect and retain sensitive personal data such as
•Details on a scenario that may be sensitive or be deemed private and confidential, or one of the protected characteristics under the equality act.
In these scenarios, we will ask for your explicit consent, and you may withdraw this consent at any time.
Marketing
From time to time, we may wish to send marketing and promotional information to our clients, or proposed clients.
If you do not wish to receive any marketing from us, you may withdraw your consent at any time by unsubscribing through our email system.
You may unsubscribe at any time.
Who we share your personal data with
We share your data with a variety of other parties during the course of conducting our business, in a number of ways, for a number of reasons.
They are as follows:
•Third party services providers who perform work on our behalf (e.g. auditors, accountants, HR consultants, IT companies)
•Tax and local authorities to enable us to comply with laws and regulations
•Marketing technology providers
How we safeguard your personal data
We make sure that all of your date is safe by using a range of technical safeguards.
We also ensure that operationally we are sound and have carefully followed procedures and awareness within the business.
We train our staff regularly and ensure we refresh knowledge when and where necessary.
In addition to these day to day safeguards, we also have a process in place to deal with any suspected breach of data.
If you suspect that your data has been misused, or has been compromised please contact us immediately at privacy@hampshireflag.co.uk
Keeping Your Data
We promise that we will never retain the data we hold on you longer than we need it.
Sometimes we have to keep your data to comply with tax, legal or regulatory issues.
For the purposes of this policy, relevant contact means:
•Communicating with us via email, telephone or mail
•Ordering and/or repeat ordering of products.
•Contacting us for information and updates on our products or services.
Cookies
Our website stores a number of different cookies on the computer or device that you use to access our website. Cookies are small text files used by browsers to store small bits of information about a device or computer, such as preferred settings or preferred languages. Cookies do not take up much space (unless you have thousands of them) and cannot contain viruses or other harmful code.
The majority of our cookies are category 2 cookies, although other websites/services that we use, such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, YouTube and Vimeo, may store category 3 cookies on your computer when you visit our website or share content.
Complaints Procedure
If you wish to complain about this privacy notice or any of the procedures set out in it please contact us on our dedicated email address which is monitored by a trained individual:
privacy@hampshireflag.co.uk. You also have the right to raise concerns with the Information Commissioner’s Office on 0303 123 1113 or at https://ico.org.uk/concerns/, or any other relevant supervisory authority should your personal data be processed outside of the UK, if you believe that your data protection rights have not been adhered to.
Contact Us
By post:
Hampshire Flag Company LTD,
Unit 11,
Pipers Wood Industrial Park,
Waterberry Drive,
Waterlooville,
Hampshire,
PO7 7XU
By email:
privacy@hampshireflag.co.uk
Some Of Our Customers
Hampshire Flag Company
Contacts
Information
Returns Policy
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
Request a Brochure
Make a Complaint
Hampshire Flag Company Ltd, Unit 11, Pipers Wood
Industrial Park, Waterberry Drive, Waterlooville,
Hampshire PO7 7XU England. © Copyright 2017 | Registered Company Number: 4359902 | VAT Number 339361641 | ISO 9001:2008 Certificate 206826 | Member Of The Flag Institute
×
Home
Flags
National & Regional Flags
Car Flags
Ceremonial Flags
Funeral Coffin Drapes
Hand Waving Flags
Novelty Flags (5ft X 3ft)
Banner Arms (Post Mount)
Banner Arms (Wall Mount)
